



JavaScript, jQuery



Adobe Creative Cloud

Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign,





PHP, Python, R, InVision, Justinmind MySQL, Java, C++

I'm a **UI/UX Designer** with over a year of experience designing simple & enriching digital solutions. My passion lies in bridging the gap between Innovative Technology and Social Impact through the power of Design.



EXPERIENCE

## **UX Design Intern**

GE Energy Connections, Redmond, WA | June 2016 - Present

- Currently working on redesigning e-terrasimulator Dispatcher Training Simulator (DTS) a software training system used by electrical power grid operators.
- Based on a corporate-wide initiative to transform legacy software into new versions that more closely align with modern usability & interface design standards (i.e. GE's Predix Design System), the project entails the creation & design of new features & functionality as well as overall user experience improvements.

## **UX Designer/Developer**

Joomla, Seattle, WA | July 2015 - March 2016

- Worked with various volunteers around the world on a redesign (usability & interface) project for the next web versions of Joomla CMS, Joomla 3.5 (successful release in March 2016), as part of the product development roadmap.
- Participated in various web & mobile redesign projects (including front-end implementation) related to Joomla.org & <u>Joomla.com</u> - Joomla's primary domains - as part of an initiative to improve user sign up rates as well as branding.



## SELECTED INDEPENDENT PROJECTS

Redesign Project for INRIX Traffic | May 2016

- Conducted a small-scale redesign project for INRIX Traffic (Android) a navigation mobile application that strives to improve users' commute by providing them with the best routes & directions.
- Conducted user research via a combination of comparative analysis, heuristic analysis, interviews, and mental modelling. Produced a set of low/high-fidelity redesign solutions for a number of identified features, based on research findings.

Usability Study for Amazon Web Services Internet of Things | January 2016 – March 2016

- Designed & conducted a baseline usability study for Amazon Web Services Internet of Things (AWS IoT) a cloud service that lets connected hardware devices easily & securely interact with cloud applications as well as other devices.
- Participated in every stage of the process's timeline: project scoping/planning, user persona profiling, participant recruitment, usability testing, data collection/analysis, and final result presentation.
- In a team of four, successfully presented final study results to the AWS IoT team at the conclusion of the project.

EDUCATION

## MS in Information Management (User Experience Research & Design)

**University of Washington, Seattle** | September 2015 – Present

**BA in International Studies** (International Political Economy & Business)

University of Washington, Seattle | September 2012 – June 2014





